<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jarosław Pawlak</title>
    <link>https://jaropawlak.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jarosław Pawlak</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 17:50:49 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jaropawlak.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s GO</title>
      <link>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/lets_go/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 17:50:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/lets_go/</guid>
      <description>C# is a great language. Each new version takes best solutions from other languages and keeps it very modern. However writing C# all the time both at work and at home feels boring sometimes. I like learning new languages as this provides good exercise. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write a simple go program. And because I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a better idea I took an app that I had already written in .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Forms Binary Size</title>
      <link>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/xamarin-forms-binary-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 20:01:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/xamarin-forms-binary-size/</guid>
      <description>Apps on iOS are nice, Xcode is fine development environment and working in it is fun. I have and app on iOS which I would like to port also to Android. I thought about rewriting it in Xamarin.Forms.
It turned out Xamarin apps (now as a part of Visual Studio) are also nice to write. I choose Xamarin.Forms to minimize code needed per platform. App is available on github: https://github.com/jaropawlak/MyExpenses.Xamarin and has almost all functionality my original app had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coredata With Cloudkit</title>
      <link>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/coredata-with-cloudkit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 22:01:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/coredata-with-cloudkit/</guid>
      <description>With iOS 13 we&amp;rsquo;ll get new cool feature - coredata db with cloudkit backup. Exactly what I need.
Bad news is that my old device will not get the update.
My doctor said that I should track food I eat. What I should do is divide my day into 2-3 hour windows and eat a small meal in every one of them. And write it down and then show it to the doctor so we can talk about what I should and what I should not eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudkitjs</title>
      <link>https://jaropawlak.com/draft/cloudkitjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 22:02:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaropawlak.com/draft/cloudkitjs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jaropawlak.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 06:12:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaropawlak.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer working with .NET Framework for more then 15 years now. I remember version 1.0 and have worked with all versions. I also write software for iOS. And desktop apps.
And console apps.
And webapps in other technologies.
And other stuff :)
My first computer was ATARI 65XE with BASIC interpreter on board. I was 7 years old. I was hooked with first line of code which might have looked like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 06:31:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaropawlak.com/2019/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Jaroslaw and this is my first post.
Usually, beginning learning new programming language starts with &amp;ldquo;Hello, World&amp;rdquo; application, therefore I&amp;rsquo;ll start with Hello World post.
This blog is generated with hugo content generator and is hosted as a github page. I&amp;rsquo;m using automatic deployment, setup can be found here: https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-github/. If you see it, it means it worked like a charm ;).
Well then&amp;hellip;
Hello, World</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>